{
    "Questions": [
      {
        "id": "1",
        "question": "What is 1+1 ?",
        "choices" : ["2", "3","4"],
        "right-answer": "2"
      },
      {
        "id": "2",
        "question": "What is 3+1 ?",
        "choices" : ["2", "3","4"],
        "right-answer": "4"
      },
      {
        "id": "3",
        "question": "What is 5+4 ?",
        "choices" : ["9", "12","8"],
        "right-answer": "9"
      },
      {
        "id": "4",
        "question": "What is 9+1 ?",
        "choices" : ["12", "11","10"],
        "right-answer": "10"
      },
      {
        "id": "5",
        "question": "What is 10+12 ?",
        "choices" : ["22", "23","24"],
        "right-answer": "22"
      },
      {
        "id": "6",
        "question": "What is 13+33 ?",
        "choices" : ["22", "53","46"],
        "right-answer": "46"
      },
      {
        "id": "7",
        "question": "What is 53+7 ?",
        "choices" : ["60", "59","61"],
        "right-answer": "60"
      },
      {
        "id": "8",
        "question": "What is 82+10 ?",
        "choices" : ["92", "83","94"],
        "right-answer": "92"
      },
      {
        "id": "9",
        "question": "What is 94+37 ?",
        "choices" : ["122", "143","141"],
        "right-answer": "141"
      },
      {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "What is 222+44 ?",
        "choices" : ["255", "266","222"],
        "right-answer": "266"
      }
    ]
  }